A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1 FA389
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Indiana University, April 12, 1951-April 30, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 702)
- Indiana University, April 12, 1951-April 30, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 703)
- Indiana University, April 12, 1951-April 30, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 704)
- Indiana University (The Poynter Center), January 16, 1976-January 30, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 705)
- Inform (New York City), December 22, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 706)
- Inner London Education Authority, September 30, 1977-October 14, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 707)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Institute), April 4, 1945-May 20, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 708)
- Institute for Advanced Study (Princeton, New Jersey), December 16-21, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 709)
- Institute for Behavioral Research, Inc. (Maryland), April 30, 1973-January 31, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 710)
- Institute for Family Research Education, December 10, 1973-January 31, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 711)
- Institute for Psychoanalysis (Gerhart Piers and George Pollock), December 5, 1968-October 4, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 712)
- Institute for Research in Psychotherapy, April 29, 1949-July 31, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 713)
- Institute for the Study of Drug Dependence (London), December 11, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 714)
- Institute for the Study of Economic Systems, November 8, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 715)
- Institute for the Study of Health and Society (Virginia), July 30, 1969-August 6, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 716)
- Institute for the Study of World Politics, December 9-13, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 717)
- Institute of Critical Care Medicine (University of Southern California), September 24, 1976-October 1, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 718)
- Institute of International Education, November 14, 1951-May 9, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 719)
- Institute of Living (Hartford, Connecticut), February 2,1967-July 20, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 720)
- Institute of Patient Care, November 17, 1965-June 9, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 721)
- Institute of Post Graduate Education and Research (Chandigarh, India), October 28, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 722)
- Institute of Religion and Health, November 15, 1972-March 10, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 723)
- Institute of Society, Ethics and the Life Sciences (Hastings Center and Princeton Office, David K. Reeves), October 28, 1971-May 20, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 724)
- Institute on the Training for Research of Psychiatric Residents, November 13, 1958-March 5, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 725)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Institutes-Internal), November 1, 1951-August 14, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 726)
- Institutional Development Corporation (Atlanta, Georgia; Bill Milliken), August 22, 1977-September 18, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 727)
- Instituto de Investigaciones Biomedicas, UNAM (Guillermo Soberon), April 5, 1968-August 29, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 728)
- Intermedia Systems Corporation (John O'Connell), March 6, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 729)
- Internal Revenue, August 6, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 730)
- Cross Reference Sheets (International-Inv), September 1, 1949-April 11, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 731)
- International Congress on Medical Librarianship, June 1, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 732)
- International Council for Educational Development, October 1, 1970-March 27, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 733)
- International Medical and Research Foundation, November 12, 1971-December 15, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 734)
- International Mental Health Congress, July 15, 1938-January 22, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 735)
- International Nursing Services Association, Inc. (Gibson, North Carolina), September 24-28, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 736)
- International Pilot Study in Medical Education (Christine McGuire), March 29, 1968-April 4, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 737)
- International Pregnancy Advisory Service (New York), June 24, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 738)
- International Rescue Committee (Czechoslovak Refugees), October 2, 1967-December 9, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 739)
- International Task Force on World Health Manpower, January 29, 1970-May 28, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 740)
- Investor Responsibility Research Center, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), September 15, 1972-September 14, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 741)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Io-Iz), January 6, 1950-April 16, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 742)
- University of Iowa, November 2, 1951-August 20, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 743)
- Irvine, Sir James, June 17, 1952-August 28, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 744)
- Irvington House (Angelo Taranta), February 25, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 745)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Jaa-Jac), October 10, 1951-December 6, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 746)
- Jackson, Marvin A., August 18, 1964-December 10, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 747)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Jad-Jay), September 29, 1952-August 14, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 748)
- Jaffe, Federick S. (China Trip Notes), October 13, 1977-August 21, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 749)
- Jakira Associates, September 10, 1975-October 10, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 750)
- Jarvik, Murray Elias, September 14, 1954-August 25, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 751)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Je-Ji), September 29, 1950-November 14, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 752)
- Jefferson Medical School of Thomas Jefferson University, December 4, 1963-December 12, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 753)
- Jensen, Frode, January 9, 1969-July 1, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 754)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Job-Joh), March 19, 1948-September 9, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 755)
- Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - Health Services (Kerr White), January 23, 1968-February 4, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 756)
- Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - Home and Office Care Program, January 1, 1951-September 20, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 757)
- Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - School of Medicine, January 1, 1949-February 12, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 758)
- Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - School of Medicine, January 1, 1949-February 12, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 759)
- Johns Hopkins University School of Hygiene and Public Health - School of Medicine, January 1, 1949-February 12, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 760)
- Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine (Albert L. Lehninger), January 8, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 761)
- Johnson, Richard, April 22, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 762)
- Johnson, Robert, July 19, 1968-February 10, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 763)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Joi-Joh), September 25, 1944-January 21, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 764)
- Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training, December 1, 1964-May 10, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 765)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Jor-Joy), March 13, 1952-December 16, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 766)
- Jordan, Robert, January 6, 1959-March 30, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 767)
- Jordan, William, July 13, 1973-July 1, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 768)
- Journal of Medical Education, May 22, 1959-March 12, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 769)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ju-Jy), November 1, 1950-March 30, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 770)
- Juilliard School, May 19, 1972-February 9, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 771)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Kaa-Kam), April 14, 1952-October 3, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 772)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Lua-Lur), April 20, 1950-August 8, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 773)
- Luco, J. V., September 11-22, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 774)
- Luft, John, August 3, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 775)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Lus-Ly), May 11, 1951-December 18, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 776)
- Lutheran Medical Center (Brooklyn, New York), June 5, 1969-March 2, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 777)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Maa-Mac), March 11, 1949-December 1, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 778)
- Mackintosh, James M., September 8, 1943-May 6, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 779)
- MacLeod, Colin M., May 19, 1966-May 2, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 780)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mad-Mai), June 21, 1951-July 22, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 781)
- Madison County Health and Hospital Unit, June 13-21, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 782)
- Maquire, Andrew, June 16, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 783)
- Mahoney, Margaret, March 26, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 784)
- Maimonides Hospital (Brooklyn, New York), February 27, 1957-March 7, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 785)
- Maine Medical School, July 10, 1959-May 1, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 786)
- Maine Regional Medical Program, July 23, 1970-October 14, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 787)
- University of Maine, March 12, 1964-February 25, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 788)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Maj-Mang), Septemer 17, 1952-July 18, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 789)
- Malayan Medical Association (Kuala Lumpur), March 30, 1971-April 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 790)
- Malpractice, March 29, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 791)
- University of Manchester (Patrick S. Byrne), October 29, 1952-July 23, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 792)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Manh-Map), February 8, 1951-July 9, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 793)
- Manitoba University, October 2, 1951-October 15, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 794)
- Manitus, Andrzej (University of Gdansk, Poland), February 15-22, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 795)
- Manpower, January 13, 1971-July 3, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 796)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mara-Mari), March 8, 1951-August 22, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 797)
- Marcus, Grace F., February 13, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 798)
- Marcuse, James E., July 14, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 799)
- Margulies, Harold D., January 3, 1968-April 4, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 800)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mark-Marr), April 2, 1951-July 29, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 801)
- Marlborough School of Music (Rudolf Serkin and Margaret R. Spanel), April 8, 1973-May 12, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 802)
- Marquette University (School of Medicine), May 8, 1956-March 5, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 803)
- Marquette University (School of Medicine), May 8, 1956-March 5, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 804)
- Marquette University (School of Medicine), March 5-12, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 805)
- Marriage Council of Philadelphia, Inc., November 19, 1971-December 9, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 806)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mars-Mart), September 19, 1951-January 31, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 807)
- Martinez, Alfonso, May 9-11, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 808)
- Maryland University, January 1, 1949-June 7, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 809)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mas), May 3, 1951-December 30, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 810)
- Massachusetts General Hospital, February 24, 1949-August 30, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 811)
- Massachusetts General Hospital (Educational Program), February 28, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 812)
- Massachusetts General Hospital (Nurse Practitioner Training, John P. Connelly), March 10, 1967-April 14, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 813)
- Massachusetts General Hospital (Nurse Practitioner Training, John P. Connelly), March 10, 1967-April 14, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 814)
- Massachusetts General Hospital/Kennedy Center ("Bunker Hill, USA"), January 13-26, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 815)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, October 2, 1950-April 13, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 816)
- Massachusetts Memorial Hospitals, April 9, 1951-October 31, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 817)
- University of Massachusetts, November 17, 1970-September 20, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 818)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mat-Maw), August 14, 1951-December 15, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 819)
- Maurer, Sidney W. Jr. (Health Care in Rural Areas), December 2, 1968-November 9, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 820)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Max-May), February 16, 1951-January 15, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 821)
- Maynard, Martha Benton, April 25, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 822)
- Mayo Foundation (Mayo Clinic and Rochester Methodist Hospital), May 25, 1980-September 23, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 823)
- Mayo Medical School, January 27, 1970-November 12, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 824)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Mayo Foundation, Box 191-192, Folders 1794-1799.
- Cross Reference Sheets (McA-McC), April 19, 1951-April 24, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 825)
- Cross Reference Sheets (McD-McI), February 25, 1948-October 17, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 826)
- McGill University, February 17, 1954-June 13, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 827)
- Cross Reference Sheets (McK-McM), November 13, 1950-October 30, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 828)
- McKeown, Dr. Thomas, July 13, 1972-September 21, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 829)
- McMaster University, February 10, 1975-January 5, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 830)
- Cross Reference Sheets (McN-McW), May 12, 1949-March 30, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 831)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mea-Medicai), December 15, 1944-October 31, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 832)
- Meade, T. D., December 4, 1975-February 4, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 833)
- Mears, D. D., September 9, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 834)
- Measurement and Evaluation of Medical Education and Medical Care, No Date (Box 49, Folder 835)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Cornell University, Box 88-91, Folder 809-830.
- Medicaid-Medicare, December 9, 1966-March 27, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 836)
- Symposium on Medicaid (New York), November 20, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 837)
- Cross Reference Sheets - Medical, May 3, 1949-November 13, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 838)
- Medical Assistance Advisory Council, May 3, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 839)
- Medical Care and Educational Foundation, Inc. (Leona Baumgartner), July 10, 1969-August 4, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 840)
- Medical College of Georgia, March 16, 1958-March 11, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 841)
- Medical College of Ohio at Toledo, August 19, 1969-February 4, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 842)
- Medical College of Pennsylvania, June 15, 1970-November 27, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 843)
  Women's Medical College of Pennsylvania as of July 1, 1970.
- Medical College of Pennsylvania (Center for Women in Medicine), November 21, 1974-November 18, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 844)
- Medical College of Pennsylvania (Center for Women in Medicine), November 21, 1974-November 18, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 845)
- Medical College of North Carolina, March 5, 1953-December 2, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 846)
- Medical College of Virginia, November 2, 1953 to December 1, 1953; February 1, 1956 to September 2, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 847)
- Medical College of Virginia, November 2, 1953 to December 1, 1953; February 1, 1956 to September 2, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 848)
- Medical College of Wisconsin (Milwaukee), January 13, 1971-November 12, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 849)
- Medical Forms (Harkness Fellowships), July 9, 1968-September 13, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 850)
- Medical Press, March 30, 1953-April 2, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 851)
- Medical Self-Care Magazine (Tom Ferguson), June 19-23, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 852)
- Medical Society of the State of New York, November 30, 1971-December 1, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 853)
- Medical World News, October 16, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 854)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Medicare-Mek), February 11, 1949-December 11, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 855)
- Medicine in the Public Interests, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), April 25, 1974-September 21, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 856)
- Meetings Papers, November 13, 1958-January 15, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 857)
- Meharry Medical College, June 24, 1948-November 24, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 858)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Meharry Medical College, Boxes 196-197, Folders 1843-1849.
- Meharry Medical College, June 24, 1948-November 24, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 859)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mel-Men), September 26, 1949-July 15, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 860)
- University of Melbourne, January 29, 1964-April 5, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 861)
- Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, February 6, 1974-July 22, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 862)
- Menninger Foundation, December 8, 1952-November 27, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 863)
- Menninger Foundation, December 8, 1952-November 27, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 864)
- Menon, Shanker K., December 10, 1953-May 10, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 865)
- Mental Health Law Project, December 10, 1973-April 22, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 866)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mer), February 7, 1951-October 31, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 867)
- Mercer University (School of Medicine), June 24, 1975-July 1, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 868)
- Samuel Merritt Hospital, March 30, 1960-April 6, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 869)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mes-Mex), October 29, 1952-May 6, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 870)
- Methodist Hospital (Mays, Kansas), September 27, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 871)
- Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, August 9, 1951-December 2, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 872)
- Mettler, Fred A., September 11, 1964-October 1, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 873)
- Mexican-American Health Problems, April 4, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 874)
- University of Mexico (Medical School), May 5-7, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 875)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mey), August 6, 1953-November 15, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 876)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mia-Millb), June 17, 1948-October 24, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 877)
- University of Miami, April 8, 1953-February 4, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 878)
- University of Miami, April 8, 1953-February 4, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 879)
- University of Miami, April 8, 1953-February 4, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 880)
- Michael Reese Medical Center (Chicago, Illinois), September 20, 1974-September 30, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 881)
- Michigan State University, February 25, 1952-September 19, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 882)
- Michigan State University (College of Human Medicine), June 4, 1976-August 11, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 883)
- Michigan State University (Video Tape Recordings for Medical Education), March 17, 1967-August 14, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 884)
- University of Michigan (William H. Beierwaltes - Thyroid Studies), December 17, 1957-December 28, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 885)
- University of Michigan (Medical Center - Child Development Project, Selma Fraiberg), March 6, 1972-March 21, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 886)
- University of Michigan (Medical Center - Community Medicine), July 29, 1969-May 8, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 887)
- University of Michigan (School of Public Health), June 26, 1953-September 10, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 888)
- Middlesex Hospital and Medical School (London), June 17, 1948-September 21, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 889)
- Midelfort, C. F., January 11, 1955-July 19, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 890)
- Midwestern Board for Medical and Allied Education (St. Paul, Minnesota), December 22, 1971-April 12, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 891)
- Milhorat, Ade T., September 10, 1941-December 5, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 892)
- Cross Reference Sheets - Miller, February 16, 1951-June 9, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 893)
- Miller, George E., February 8, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 894)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Milero-Milw), April 20, 1951-January 21, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 895)
- Millsaps College (Jackson, Mississippi), November 2, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 896)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Min-Mis), September 15, 1950-November 20, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 897)
- Minnesota Psychiatric Institute, February 1-15, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 898)
- University of Minnesota, November 20, 1947-March 23, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 899)
- University of Minnesota, November 20, 1947-March 23, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 900)
- University of Minnesota (Community Health-Care Center), September 12, 1968-October 29, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 901)
- University of Minnesota (School of Medicine, Duluth), September 15, 1969-March 24, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 902)
- University of Minnesota (Visscher, Maurice B.), January 4, 1973-July 10, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 903)
- Mirsky, Arthur, March 11, 1947-October 22, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 904)
- Mississippi State Board of Health, April 29, 1952-September 2, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 905)
- Mississippi University, June 3, 1955-February 12, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 906)
- University of Missouri (Kansas City), December 9, 1975-October 24, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 907)
- University of Missouri (School of Medicine), June 11, 1964-July 19, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 908)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mit-Miz), October 11, 1951-October 12, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 909)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Moa-Mol), March 22, 1951-October 2, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 910)
- Model Practice Act for the Health Professions, May 31, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 911)
- Modern Woodmen of America, October 12-27, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 912)
- Mohler, William C. (Computers in Clinical Medicine), October 17-23, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 913)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mon), May 20, 1952-September 24, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 914)
- Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center, September 23, 1971-December 9, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 915)
- Montreal University, August 31, 1954-July 31, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 916)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Moo), July 14, 1949-November 19, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 917)
- Moodie, William, February 15, 1952-October 22, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 918)
- Moore, Francis D., April 23, 1953-February 19, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 919)
- Moore, Robert A., October 9, 1962-April 1, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 920)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mora-Mori), September 14, 1951-October 24, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 921)
- Morehouse College, February 5, 1973-September 27, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 922)
- Morison, Robert S., December 14, 1971-March 29, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 923)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Morr-Mory), March 24, 1952-March 17, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 924)
- Morristown Memorial Adolescent Clinic (New Jersey), April 23, 1973-May 29, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 925)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mos-Moy), November 13, 1950-April 6, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 926)
- Mount Sinai Hospital, February 15, 1960-September 18, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 927)
- Mount Sinai Hospital, February 15, 1960-September 18, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 928)
- Mount Sinai Hospital, February 15, 1960-September 18, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 929)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine (The City University of New York), November 12, 1964-February 15, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 930)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine (The City University of New York), November 12, 1964-February 15, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 931)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mua-Mur), December 28, 1948-February 12, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 932)
- Murphy, E. J., January 5, 1954-March 1, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 933)
- Murphy, John Milne, March 10, 1955-April 13, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 934)
- Murphy, Lois, January 19, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 935)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Mus-My), August 2, 1951-October 30, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 936)
- Myrin Institute, Inc. (New York), January 2-17, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 937)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Nab-Nath), April 2, 1951-March 10, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 938)
- Nachman, Ralph L. (New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center), November 12, 1968-February 13, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 939)
- Name Cards, October 24, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 940)
- Cross Reference Sheets - National (A-C), January 17, 1951-June 17, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 941)
- National Academy of Sciences (Institute of Medicine), April 17, 1970-December 23, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 942)
- National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council (Division of Behavioral Science), February 24, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 943)
- National Academy of Sciences/National Research Council (Division of Medical Sciences - Drug Research Board), July 7, 1967-June 13, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 944)
- National Achievement Scholarship Program, October 21, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 945)
- National Advisory Commission on Health Manpower, November 1, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 946)
- National Association for Advancement of Colored People, April 29, 1968-May 9, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 947)
- National Association for Mental Health, Inc., June 19, 1952-January 15, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 948)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, National Association for Mental Hygiene, Boxes 219-220, Folders 2066-2067).
- National Association of Advisors for the Health Professions (Michigan), April 21, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 949)
- National Association of Blue Cross Shield Plans, November 15, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 950)
- National Audubon Society, January 29, 1960-July 21, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 951)
- National Board of Medical Examiners, May 12, 1953-May 9, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 952)
- National Board of Medical Examiners, May 12, 1953-May 9, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 953)
- National Center for Health Education, April 3, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 954)
- National Center for Health Services Research and Development (Paul J. Sanazaro), September 25, 1967-June 16, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 955)
- National Center for Prevention and Treatment of Child Abuse, October 14, 1971-November 22, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 956)
- National Clearinghouse for Mental Health Information, February 8, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 957)
- National Commission on Accrediting, November 16, 1953-June 19, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 958)